In this video, we will introduce you to the new features in the Marvelous Designer 12.2 version.
Now we will pull the view to the virtual model leg to see the roll effect.
Go to the 2D window and select the edit sheet tool.
Press the Shift key to select all the lines that form a side pants corner.
Here we select the bottom line of the front and back of the left leg of the pants.
Press the right mouse button to find the roll function in the pop-up menu.
After clicking the roll, it will pop up the dialogue box that sets the number of numbers.
You can set the roll count to a maximum of three times.
This is the total number of folds and rolls.
The bottom is the distance, that is, the size of the roll area.
When you set the value, you will see the green original version in the 3D window.
You can refer to it to refer to the location of the edge after the roll.
When we modify the value, this green original version will also follow the movement, which is convenient for you to refer to.
Finally, I set the roll count to three times.
The distance is 31 mm.
Click apply to apply the roll effect in the 3D window.
If the position of the roll is not suitable at the end, I can click reset to make it return to the initial state.
If it is suitable, then click off.
If the particle diameter of the roll sheet is higher than 10 mm, it will automatically be modified to 10 mm for a more stable simulation.
Then the red simulation to apply the roll effect.
You can see that although it uses a symmetrical relationship, the roll effect only works on the side of choosing the roll.
At present, the roll effect cannot be created by link or symmetrical relationship.
Now we will perform the same steps on the other side of the board.
Press the Shift key to select the two lines of the right corner.
Select roll. Here you can see that the value I set before has been automatically recorded, so we can click apply.
Click off to close the window and then activate simulation.
The application roll effect and the simulation effect are more natural.
Now the two corners are rolled.
You can also set different values for them.
This will create an uneven effect.
Compared to the previous method of rolling the board, this function is faster.
As you can see, it only takes a few seconds to roll the board.
Please note that the roll function cannot be used on the outside of the board that is in the relationship with the sewing line.
Here, the sleeve is sewed and a sleeve cuff cannot be used to roll.